https://www.microfridge.com/privacy/

You are here: Home / Privacy
Privacy
Effective April 30, 2010
Introduction
Your (“You” or “Your”) privacy concerns are important to Intirion Corporation (“Us”, “We” or “Our”), and protecting Your privacy and safeguarding Your information is one of Our highest goals. You need to know what information is being collected about You through Our website (“Site”) and how Your information may be used. To that end, this Privacy Policy explains what information We may collect about You.
Collection of Information
In connection with Your use of the Site, You will provide the majority of the information We collect about You. For example, We may require You to provide certain information, including, but not limited to, Your name, mailing address, e-mail addresses, telephone number, language preference, model numbers, and other personally identifiable information. Other information collected by Us may be provided automatically when You access the Site, such as observing Your use of the Site, through the use of cookies (described below), and may be obtained from other sources such as Our business partners. We do not require you provide personal information to visit our Web site; however, You may choose to provide Us with personal information through an email message, form, order checkout process, survey, registration process, etc. This information is used only to fulfill the stated purpose of Your communication, order, participation, or use of certain aspects of the Site.
No Collection of Children’s Personal Information
Our Sites are intended for general audiences and commercial use. We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13. We reserve the right to delete any information We believe to be in violation of this Privacy Policy.
Use of Information
We automatically collect and temporarily store information about Your visit. The information We collect enables Us to refine and offer better services and information to You. We may share the information We collect about You with Our business partners. The types of information we collect include, but are not limited to:
the date and time of Your visit;
IP addresses;
browser type, operating system, and language;
the pages you visited; and
the address of the Web site from which You came.
Cookies
When You visit the Site, We may place a text file called a “cookie” on Your computer’s hard drive. A cookie is a small piece of information that a website can store on Your web browser and later retrieve. A cookie enables the Site to recognize You as a prior user, provides the Site with information regarding Your prior use and assists Us in determining what portions of the Site are most appropriate for You. Your Web browser may provide You with the ability to not accept cookies. However, in order to take full advantage of the Site, We recommend that You accept cookies from the Site.
Disclosure
We do not sell, license, lease or otherwise disclose Your information to any other parties; except that We may share Your information with our partners with Your consent. We also may disclose Your information when We believe, in good faith, that disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with laws, law enforcement or court orders, or to protect the rights, property or safety of another person, including Our own property or rights.
We will make every effort to discontinue the use of Your information as soon as practicable if requested by You. We may need to retain information in Our archives and records to comply with law, resolve disputes, analyze problems, assist with any investigations, enforce Our policies, and take other actions otherwise permitted or required by law.
No Liability
We have made significant investments in protecting and safeguarding Your information. We continuously upgrade and enhance Our security measures as new tools, techniques and technology become available. However, We do not guaranty that any such information will not be misused or disclosed to third parties. We will not have any liability to You for any such misuse or disclosure. If You choose to purchase a product or service offered by another company, any information You share with that company will not be controlled by this Privacy Policy, You do so at Your own risk, and We have no liability to You. You understand that electronic communications may be accessed by unauthorized parties when communicated across the Internet, network communications facilities, or other electronic means. You agree that We are not responsible for any electronic communication and/or any of your data which may be lost, altered, intercepted or stored without authorization during the transmission of any data whatsoever across networks not owned and/or operated by Us.
Consent
By using the Site, You consent to the collection and use of Your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. If We decide to change this Privacy Policy, which We may do at any time without notice to You, We will post those changes on this page. By continuing to use the Site after We have posted the changes, You agree to and accept such changes. You should periodically check the Site for changes to this Privacy Policy.
Additional Information
We welcome Your questions, comments and requests for additional information regarding privacy of the Site.
You accept and agree to be bound this Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions of Use.
Don't miss MicroFridge® Events in your area!
